Discover the secret of the Surfer.
Fantastic Four: Rise of the Silver Surfer is a science fiction,
adventure, action film directed by Tim Story.
The Fantastic Four return to the big screen as a new and
all powerful enemy threatens the Earth.
The seemingly unstoppable 'Silver Surfer', but all is not what it seems and there are old and
new enemies that pose a greater threat than the intrepid superheroes realize.
Reed Richards / Mr. Fantastic, played by Ioan Gruffudd.
Sue Richards / Invisible Woman, played by Jessica Alba.
Johnny Storm / Human Torch, played by Chris Evans.
Ben Grimm / The Thing, played by Michael Chiklis.
Victor von Doom / Doctor Doom, played by Julian McMahon.
Norrin Radd / Silver Surfer (voice), played by Laurence Fishburne.
Fantastic Four: Rise of the Silver Surfer is a 2007 superhero film based
on the Marvel Comics superhero team the Fantastic Four.
The sequel to the 2005 film, it was directed by Tim Story,
from a screenplay by Don Payne and Mark Frost.
The film stars Ioan Gruffudd, Jessica Alba, Chris Evans, and Michael Chiklis as the title characters, with Julian
McMahon, Kerry Washington, Andre Braugher, Beau Garrett, Doug Jones and Laurence Fishburne in supporting roles.
The plot follows the Fantastic Four (and Doctor Doom) as they
confront the Silver Surfer to save Earth from Galactus.
The film was released in the United States on June 15, 2007, to generally mixed reviews and grossed $301.9 million worldwide
and was a box-office success, but earned less than its predecessor which grossed $333.5 million worldwide.
A third film was planned but ultimately cancelled.
The series was rebooted in 2015 with the release of Fantastic
Four to poor critical and commercial reception.
Marvel Studios eventually reclaimed the film rights of the characters, along with the
X-Men and Deadpool, after the acquisition of 21st Century Fox by Disney.
Evans, who would portray Captain America in the Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU), reprised his role as Johnny Storm / Human Torch in the 2024 film Deadpool
& Wolverine, with Joseph Quinn taking over the role in the MCU in The Fantastic Four: First Steps and soon to be in Avengers: Doomsday.
The film explores themes of mask, surfboard, helicopter, fire, airplane.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.